### Menus OS BASIC Shell v4.4.3 for the TI-84 Plus CE ###
	by calclover2514

## Features

	- Enables Lowercase Letters
	- Includes Asm(prgmUNDONE), which, when run at the end of a program or before the Stop command, will eliminate the Done message at the end of any program
	- Includes the choice to enable irregular symbols by running prgmSYMBOLS
	- Includes a Command Line and a Graphical OS
	- CLI (Command Line Interface) includes over 25 commands
	- Able to set Time, Date, Background Color, Background Picture, Theme Color, etc...
	- Features many Games, including Minecraft and Pokémon
	- Features many programs, including a 3D Graphing Tool and an on-calc painting program (TI-Paint)
	- Written on a calculator in the BASIC editor
	- Well tested
	- About 98% BASIC, with very little assembly
	- Includes optional support for the TI-Innovator Hub
	- Features a false fingerprint scanner
	- Built-in virus scanner will remind you to scan your calculator once a month

## Warnings

	- Highly Complex for BASIC (includes over 175 files)
	- Requires TI-OS v5.3 or higher
	- Only works on TI-84+CE and NOT on TI-84+CSE because of assembly files
	- Will reset some minor settings (graph zoom, border color, MATHPRINT, etc...)
	- Cannot be run from Cesium
	- Will not fit in RAM, so send to Archive
	- Change code at your own risk!!!

## Troubleshooting

	- If lowercase letters stop working, just run prgmLWRCASE
	- If Menus stops working at all, reinstall it by deleting the following lists and running prgm AAAMENUS: ⌊GUI and ⌊MENUS
	- If CLI stops working, launch Menus and press f2 in BIOS screen

## How to Use

	- Send all program files to your calculator with TI Connect CE or TILP II v1.18 or later
	- Run prgmAAAMENUS and complete the installation process and first time setup
	- Press [^] for help in OS
	- Type HELP for a full list of commands in CLI
	- Type [clear] while in fake fingerprint scanner to exit
	- While in CLI, type MAN [command name] for more help with that command
	- The Clean Calc option in RamTidy is fully configurable, Matrices are Minecraft savegames and are therefore unchecked by default
	- Press [del] while in the OS to uninstall Menus (This will not delete it, only uninstall it)
	- Press the side arrows or [window] and [trace] in Graphical OS to change the border color
	- While in Graphical OS, Press [y=] to access RamTidy and [graph] to access ViruScan
	- While in Graphical OS, Press [alpha], [)] to lock screen (If you have no password, the password is "0")
	- To exit any fake home screen, simply type QT
	- If you are unsure whether you are in a fake home screen or not, press the [prgm] button. If it opens a list of programs, you are in the real home screen; otherwise, the home screen is fake
	- Feel free to use and change code if you know what you are doing
	- If you are not sure how to exit a program or loop, try pressing [del], [clear], [mode], or [enter]
	- BIOS Commands:
		. f1	Boot Order: Select the default boot
		. f2	Clear CLI History: Deletes CLI history
		. f4	Esc: Prematurely exits the BIOS and shuts down
		. f5	Boot Menu: Select one time boot or enter Password Recovery Tool
		. f3	System Info: In OS Only, Program Version and Activation ID (If signed in)
	- Most importantly, have fun!

## Activation ID

	- The code is:  JLIKQ-IQIQP-O649U-KQOVU-VTU16-4000A (Include dashes when typing it in to the calc)
	- This is used when installing and recovering Menus OS
	- This code is the only thing that can save you from forgetting your password

## Release Notes

	- 4/21/2018: First Release...
	- 4/26/2018: Fixed small, rare bug with installer
	- 5/04/2018: Added an extra setting option and updated installer
	- 6/13/2018: Added extra installer features and minimally reduced size
	- 6/23/2018: Added BIOS, Boot Functions, Recovery Tool, Hub and Calc Detection, and much more, as well as reducing size
	- 7/18/2018: Reduced size and fixed major bug with Minesweeper
