(C) SM84CE

This is a timer for the TI-84 Plus CE's and TI-84 Plus CSE's.  This is a fairly easy to use utility, the menu options are self-explainatory.  This utility can currently do a stopwatch and a timer.  If you have any questions, comments or suggestions, PM me at cemetech.net or post a revew on cemetech.net.

Sending: Send **ALL** 3 programs in this ZIP to your Ti-84 Plus CE using a calculator linking program.  

Running: Run prgmTMR from the homescreen or from your favorite shell.  If you have CE OS 5.3 or below, you need to keep prgmCLR0VAR and prgmθFMT in the RAM.  If you have CE OS 5.3, you can put all 3 programs in the Archive.


Enjoy!

**Upload 2, fixed bug where functions were graphed before the program formatted.  Also tested CSE compatability.